linkcentre.com 2018-05-13

# LinkCentre.com Privacy Policy

This policy applies to the services and web pages within the [LinkCentre.com](https://www.linkcentre.com/) domain.

This document should be read in conjunction with the [Interlink Advertising Limited GDPR Policy.](https://www.interlinkadvertising.co.uk/privacy)

The LinkCentre.com domain is wholly owned by Interlink Advertising Limited.

LinkCentre.com is committed to maintaining the privacy of it's users. When a user performs a search across either the Search Engine or Directory, LinkCentre.com does not store any information which could identify the user. LinkCentre.com does collect statistical information about the number of keyword and directory searches. LinkCentre.com does not store any information that could identify who performed the search.

The LinkCentre.com index holds information about web pages. The following information is voluntarily entered into the database by Web Publishers and other interested parties:

  * Web Page Title

  * Web Page Address (URL)

  * Description of Web Page

  * Name of person entering the information (optional)

  * Email address of person entering the information (optional)

  * Comments through a feedback form (optional)

  * Target Country

  * IP address used to submit listing

  * Date and Time of submission

If volunteered, the name and email address of the person entering the information is stored in order to send a confirmation email when the information has been added to the database. LinkCentre.com does not make the name, email address or IP address accessible through the web site or disclose them to any third party unless required to do so by law.

Because we want to demonstrate our commitment to our users' privacy, we disclose the following information.

  * What personally identifiable information Interlink Advertising Limited collects.
  * What personally identifiable information third parties collect through the Web site.
  * What organisation collects the information.
  * How Interlink Advertising Limited uses the information.
  * With whom Interlink Advertising Limited may share user information.
  * What choices are available to users regarding collection, use and distribution of the information.
  * What types of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under Interlink Advertising Limited control.
  * How users can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

Information Collection and Use

Interlink Advertising Limited is the sole owner of the infomation collected on our web site. Interlink Advertising Limited collects information at several different points on our Web site.

Information is collected for the purpose of displaying details of web sites within the directory. Users have the option to participate in this activity for the purposes of maintaining and securing our site, enhancing our site and product offerings, contacting by email or regular mail and telemarketing. A user must provide the clickstream information (internet protocol address, internet service provider, platform type, date/time stamp, operating system), http protocol information (last uri requested and browser type), interaction information (browser interaction such as when the mouse moves over an image), location data (current physical location), navigation and click-stream data (passive activity such as pages visited), search terms (search text), transaction information (account transactions), user's name, user's login information, user's employer, user's home contact information, user's business contact information, 3rd party name, 3rd party login information, 3rd party employer, 3rd party business contact information, business/organisation name and contact information for the business/organisation. It is optional for the user to provide User's Employer, User's Home Contact Information, User's Business Contact Information, 3rd Party Name, 3rd Party Login Information, 3rd Party Employer, 3rd Party Business Contact Information, Business/Organisation Name and Contact Information for the Business/Organisation. We encourage users to provide optional information so we can provide a more personalised experience on our site. The reason we use this information is to archive information for future reference, complete the current transaction, contact by email or regular mail, contact by telephone, enhance our site and product offerings, enhance your experience by customising our site, maintain and secure our site, understand (in aggregate) interests of website visitors and understand your interests. We retain this information as stated by our business practices. 

Cookies  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user's hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. You can set your browser to notify you to either accept or deny the cookie according to the following information. 

Our website uses cookies to enhance our site.

Profiles  
Interlink Advertising Limited uses Website data to create a profile of our users. A profile is stored information that we keep on individual users that details their viewing preferences. Consequently, collected information is tied to the users personally identifiable information to provide offers and improve the content of the site for the user. This profile is used to tailor a user's visit to our Web site, and to direct pertinent marketing promotions to them.

Communications from the Site  
When customers provide us contact information for Website (user participation is voluntary and users can opt-out by following the directions in our 'Choice' section) we use the information to contact the user to deliver sales and product information that will be useful to the them.

Sharing Information  
Legal Disclaimer  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.

Personally Identifiable Information  
Personally identifiable information _is_ shared with any third parties with opt-in user permission only.

Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)  
Aggregate information _is not_ shared with third parties.

Data Security  
Interlink Advertising Limited has physical security in our facilities to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of information. Our company uses secure encryption technology (secure socket connection) for all sensitive financial or health data transmitted on our site.

Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information  
If a user's personally identifiable information changes such as post / zip code, phone, email or postal address they can change all information. If a user wishes to correct/update information or no longer desires our service, they can notify us of what they desire by contacting us using any of the information in the Contact section of this policy.

Links and Advertisements  
Our website contains links to other sites. We have partnerships with ad server companies. We, Interlink Advertising Limited, are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any other web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

Changes to the Privacy Statement  
The information you submit to us is controlled by the privacy policy in effect at the time you submit it. If we significantly change our policy, we will post a notice in a conspicuous place on our website notifying visitors of policy changes.

Data Retention Statement  
Stated Business Practices Data retention - We keep information about you and your purchases for as long as you remain our customer. If you do not place an order from us for one year we will remove your information from our databases. Legal Requirement Data retention - We keep information about you for 4 years after you terminate employment in accordance with the employment practices established by CA EDD. Stated Purpose Data retention - We keep information about you until you have confirmed receipt of our product shipment plus the warranty period of 90 days.

Third Party Advertising  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and would like to know your options in relation to not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

Storage of financial information  
Interlink Advertising do not store credit or debit card financial details. We use ChargeBee and PayPal to process payments. 

Contact Information  
Using the following information, you can contact us if you have questions about our privacy policy.  

 | Interlink Advertising Limited  
---|---  
 | 27 Old Gloucester Street  
 | London, WC1N 3AX  
 | United Kingdom  
 |   
 | E-mail: [support@linkcentre.com](mailto:support@linkcentre.com)  
 | Phone: +44 845 838 1877  
  
Resolving Privacy Policy Disputes  
If you think we have not followed our privacy policy in some way, it can be resolved by contacting us.

Return to [Link Centre](https://www.linkcentre.com/)
